Here we go, Apkami!
This time we have with us Miki Naka of Morning Musume 23 and Honoka Kobayashi of Beyonce Seasonings.
and Honoka Kobayashi from Beyonce's Seasonings.
This show is about the behind-the-scenes of the production of various artists
This is a program that goes behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
our recordings and rehearsals.
We will show you the process of our recording and rehearsal.
So, first of all, let's take a look behind the scenes of the two mc's. Inside of me, you know.
The other day, our performance at Yokohama Arena ended without incident. Thank you very much.
Morning Musume。 23 had been on a tour since September, and we had a 2-day concert at Yokohama Arena as the final concert of the tour.
On the first day, the members of og appeared on stage and collaborated with us.
I was so happy to be able to do it with everyone.
I was so happy that we could do it together.
Mizuki Fukumura graduated and made a new troupe.
And after Mizuki Fukumura graduated, we had a new battle group.
We are Morning Musume。 23 and we will continue to do our best, so I hope you all are watching over us.
I was able to see the second day's performance, and I saw the two new members working very hard.
I was also able to see the second day's performance, and I saw the two new members working very hard, and the senior members giving wonderful performances that I really admired.
The other day, I, Kobayashi, went to see a performance of a play called "The Beauty Spy's Missing Attache Case.
I, Kobayashi, recently finished a play called "Beauty Spy Missing Attache Case" by the Women's Drama Club.
Thank you very much for your hard work!
This was my first time playing a male role.
I also played two other roles as a girl.
I was particularly impressed with the male role.
I played a male role, and he had a very calm and easygoing personality.
I was a bit out of my element in the role.
I had been working on it since the rehearsal period.
I had to break out of my shell during the rehearsal period.
I felt that my singing was very much alive after the performance.
I felt that my range of expression has expanded a lot.
I think I have grown a lot.
Yumi Ishida, a member of Morning Musume。 Yumi Ishida, a member of Morning Musume・Yumi Discal, went to see the performance of Mionji.
That's right.
She told the members how she felt about it that day.
I see.
That's why I really wanted to go see it.
If the DVD Blu-ray is released, I would like to see it.
So, let's start with this up-cam.
JuiceJuice Romance in the middle of 2023JuiceJuice version music video making
The making of the music video on JuiceJuice's official YouTube channel.
Please check out the making of 2023JuiceJuice version music video shooting on the official JuiceJuice YouTube channel!
Good morning and thank you for your cooperation.
Good morning. Good morning.
Good morning, please. Best regards.
Basically, it's going to be a music video, although you might not use your hands in a normal situation,
It's okay to do gestures and body language.
Please do it as if it were a music video.
Yes.
Feet, say the line.
If you don't lay it on your mouth first, it's great.
Oh, man, you're...
You're hunched over, you know that?
Oh, yeah.
You're really hunched over, your shoulders.
Shoulders back.
The one that sings perfume.
Feet. Say, "Line.
I have to put my mouth where my mouth is first.
Oh, my God, you're...
You're hunched over, you are.
You are.
We're shooting a music video for JuiceJuice's version of "In the Middle of Romance 2023,
We are currently filming the music video for the new version of "In the Middle of Romance 2023JuiceJuice",
I'm so excited and happy to be able to make a music video of this new version of "On the Way of Romance,
I can't wait to see the finished product,
I can't wait to see the finished product.
I'm in the process of filming my own scene,
This song is very groovy.
I could listen to it very well,
I listened to it and the drums sounded really cool,
It was cool,
I could really get into the groove.
Right?
I could get into a great groove.
Music
Today we are shooting a music video for "2023 in the middle of romance.
I kind of like sessions.
Like an automatic session.
You know, you just press the right button.
Like this.
Thank you for watching!
This was my first time to shoot a music video for one of JuiceJuice's existing songs, and I was very nervous,
I was really nervous, and I was worried about what I would do, but I saw the examples of the older members and thought how cool they looked, and I wanted to do it as soon as possible,
I had a lot of fun during the shoot, and I think it was a really good experience.
My first music video shoot was for "Plastic Love," and it was rather mature,
I tried to express a more mature look, because I had been in this kind of moody mood for a long time.
I was trying to express an adult-like mood. But Miss-chan's clear face in this colorful song was very mature and cool.
Thank you very much.
We did the lip shot at the same time...the lip scene is in the middle.
We re-recorded the lip shot and re-recorded the lip scene, so the sound is a little different from the original,
The orchestra is really good.
The soundtrack is also very good.
The orchestra is really cool. It was cool to begin with, but just by arranging it differently, the atmosphere has changed so drastically that it gives such a different impression, and I shot the lip to match.
Yes, I was very happy to be able to make a soundtrack for the album, but I never thought I would be able to shoot a music video, so I was very happy about that as well.
That doesn't happen very often.
It doesn't happen very often.
Not at all.
It was really cool to lip-synch to the music, and the orchestra was so...
It was cool.
Because I have cool eyes.
I was a little bit taller than the others.
Risa was so excited, and she was like this.
It was a totally different feeling.
The members who were filming before me were all in a groove, playing the guitar, and Risa had recently been taking salt and getting into a groove, so if you see the video of the two of us together, the sound might be a little too loud.
But I think that is also a part of the members' personalities, so I hope you will check that out and continue to do so in the future,
I think that the members have their own personalities, so I would like you to check out their personalities and look forward to seeing what will happen in the future.
I will continue to work hard. Filming.
Yes, I'm going to be in Short City now.
Please subscribe to our channel.
Say I love you.
You have to say it out loud and clear.
Oh, my God.
I still love you.
Majishun loves you, loves you, loves you...
I still love you
I still love you.
You have to say it out loud!
Oh, my God!
I still love you
Majishun loves and is loved
Yui, yui, yui
We're celebrating our 10th anniversary...
I guess you could say I'm a legend again
I'm so happy to be able to participate in the re-shooting of that song
I am very happy to be able to participate in the re-shooting of the song
I'm very happy to be a part of re-shooting the song after 10 years.
It's twice as many people and more than twice as much as we shot back then
There are twice as many people, and more than twice as many
I think it's going to be a very different atmosphere again.
I'm very curious to see what kind of expressions everyone has on their faces when they are shooting.
I'm very curious to see what kind of expressions they'll have.
I'm already in a groove.
I'm so excited that I'm forgetting what I'm singing.
The sound behind me is really changing, too.
I can't help but get on board.
I can't help but move my body naturally.
I'm doing it today under the fun music.
I'm having a lot of fun all day long.
As for me...
Kudiyume and I danced together.
I danced with Kudoyume, and we were all trying to adjust the direction of our movements and how we could move.
We were all working on adjusting the direction of our moves and adjusting our movements.
Yume and I have been together for a long time.
t
Yume and I tend to be serious, so we didn't make any adjustments,
I just let it go as it was,
I was happy with the way it came together,
I was happy with the result,
I personally like the way Omifu dances, so I was happy to see that,
I personally really like the way you dance, so I was happy to see that.
Thank you very much.
Ah!
Ugh!
Uhh!
The way Omifu dances.
Say I still love you, say it out loud, or it's gonna be bad.
I still love you
Do it, do it, do it!
Cup'n'Roll of romance
Well, that's it!
I'm done playing the lead role!
Thank you very much for the music video for Juice Juice's major label debut single, Romance no Nakamichi.
I was really happy to be able to make a music video for the song in a way that was very difficult for me to do, and to make a resistant version for Juice Juice, but...
I was really happy to make a resistant version of the music video for Juice Juice, and the original members who debuted with us at the time were all there, and the mv was amazing.
I wish you could see it again and compare it with the original version, but I thought it was very meaningful to re-do this song wearing the staggered costumes.
It was a fun and lively shoot from start to finish, and we worked up a sweat.
Thank you very much!
I was thinking that we started with 5 members and there are 11 of us in this music video shoot, but each one of us is still full of individuality, so I was really impressed by their flirtatiousness and their personality.
I think that you will be able to enjoy the juice of the present in the middle of this romance.
I think you'll get to see a lot of Juice Juice in the course of this romance.
We're shooting a new music video called "2023 Juice Juice Version" in the middle of romance.
We shot a new music video.
And all the instruments were also newly shot.
It's really fun to compare the music video with the original version.
I thought it would be a lot of fun to compare the music video with the original version.
The number of people in the band has more than doubled.
I think there's a lot more flirtatiousness now.
The first time I heard this song was at
I first heard this song at a performance of JuiceJuice and BEYONES at Heian Jingu Shrine in Kyoto.
I heard the new version of this song through my earpiece at the rehearsal.
I heard the new version through my earphones at the rehearsal.
When I heard the new version, I thought, "What? It was different from what I had heard before.
I realized that it was a re-recording.
From that moment on, it was just too cool!
I really recommend listening to it live.
I really do.
When I listen to the CD, it's like...
When I listen to a CD, I think, "Let's focus on the bass guitar now.
Next time, let's focus on the guitar.
Or, let's focus on the drums.
I think you can enjoy it in various ways.
Let's enjoy the new version of JuiceJuice's "Romance no Nakamichi" and the original version together.
Let's enjoy the new version of JuiceJuice's romance and the original version together!
That's all for the 2023 JuiceJuice version of "In the middle of the romance of JuiceJuice
Music video shooting!
Thank you very much!
Because I just have a taste for movies Tonight it's cloudy in Shibuya
I need a boyfriend or a girlfriend or someone...
I'm sure it'll be good
Next, here we go.
Morning Musume。 23 VOLUME FEVER Haruka Inoue, Ako Yumiga's dance lesson
From the latest single of Morning Musume。 23's latest single, "Supremely Fever.
Before the lesson with all the members, Haruka Inoue and Ako Yumigita had a lesson alone.
Here's a sneak peek of the lesson.
Let's take a look!
Do you know how to tilt your head a little bit, or do you know the timing when you first go into that bump?
We take turns going into the bumps in canon, and we're not timing it right.
Clap.
The timing of our entry point.
That's where we got our butts thumped in the un-pump, un-pump.
And there's a little bit of a gap between us.
And you're waiting, right? In the clap.
Waiting, and then leaning in a little bit before you bump butts.
That's right. That's right.
If you don't lean on each other, your butts won't hit each other right there.
Come in a little bit. Unh-pun.
Five, six, seh.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Tattletale, yes, yes, yes.
To bump it, it's more than what you think it feels like now.
Bend your knees a bit more during the luck, then put your butt out.
Yes, so now I'll continue with the turning part.
Five, six, intro, one.
2,3,4,5,6,7,8 1,2,se-no, lots of se-no
1,2,3,4,5,6 Guruguru, 1,2,3,4 Pan, pan, pan, pan
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8 1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8
Yes, yes, yes, yes, first of all, this movement.
This is to make the fingers stand out, so reverse the hips and the fingers.
Yes, on purpose, on purpose Even if you do it on the spot, like this, even if you don't progress
Yes, yes, yes, yes. Bend your knees a little bit more, okay?
More and more, yes, I want the fingers to stand out.
More and more, this is moving and moving and moving.
It's like it's moving.
And, um, I don't have a jacket right now.
Just, like, just slap the shoulder here, just enough to show the shoulder here.
Five, six, A-melon.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
A, boom-boom-boom-boom.
Yes, yes, yes.
When I'm singing.
I have to be a little more conscious of the face that says I'm singing.
I don't go in with the "wow" look as an extension of when I'm dancing.
And when I'm not singing, the choreography is...
The choreography for when I'm not singing is sitting like this.
I'm sitting, but if I take a break like this.
I'm already late for the next move.
Don't get on the floor here, but be ready to stand up at any time so that you can move right away.
Don't drop it like this.
The way you do the accents.
You've got to be aware of the back, back, back of the sound.
Wow, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something.
En-han, en-sui, en-sui, en-hi, circle, circle, circle, circle, circle, circle, circle, circle, circle, circle.
Okay, I'll start with the song.
5, 6, 7, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10.
10... 10... 10... 10... 10...
10, SEE-oh, Tata, watch, watch
A cup of yen, wow!
Ten, three, four, five, six, seven.
Ta-tah, ta-tah, ta-tah, ta-tah, ta-tah, ta-tah.
Ta-tah, ta-tah, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding.
Five, six, seven, eight.
Yes, that's what I just did, and I'm going to move to the next position, but I'm not going to move, I'm going to do the same thing I did before.
I'm going to remove the hips and the fingers, and I'm going to make the bend of the knees a little bit bigger.
I want to make him stand out... with this finger. Can I hear it from the head?
Yes, please.
Great, great, great.
That one person who always, always tells people.
Great, great, great!
That one lie... Until it's all over.
That I'm embracing all of my youth.
I know you.
You know better than to spend time with your family.
You better listen up.
Riffa, the rain is just a little bit...
I'm enjoying it more and more.
Riffer, just a little bit of rain.
Above all else, you want me to shine.
You're M.C.C.O.W.
You make everyone happy, even you
Wow, there's no love
Basically, I'm not sure if my mouth is moving or not in that part of the song.
I can understand the "wow" part, for example, but I can't understand the "Fever Whenever" part.
I can understand the part where he sings "Fever Whenever" in the chorus, but I can't understand the part where he sings "Fever Whenever" in the chorus.
The part where she sings "Fever Whenever" is still a little fuzzy, so I want her to move it around a little more.
I need to move it really well and firmly, not just casually "Fever".
This phrase is supposed to be the next position to move to.
I can't help but look down.
But I'm moving, but I'm not looking down.
I just check my number at the end.
If I think I'm going that way, I'll go that way first, and then I'll check my number at the end and go in.
Basically, I don't look down unless I'm told to look down in the choreography.
First of all, the lyrics
Enjoy yourself to the fullest, shine brighter than anything else, and I'm sure you'll make everyone happy.
First of all, it doesn't match the lyrics "I won't tell you.
The face has to be in line with the lyrics.
I need to have a face that matches the lyrics, but I'm not into the lyrics at all right now, so I need to practice hard, not just hard, but hard plus that, too.
I'll get it done in time for the shoot. I'll take care of that face, too.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
Wow, wow, wow.
That one battle, that one person, will change the times.
One step, one step, and it's all over.
Sleeper.
I'm a little disappointed tonight.
I just thought I'd say something tonight.
This is your year.
Don't make you and everyone else happy.
Thank you.
Thank you for watching.
Haruka Inoue and Keiko Yumi, members of the 17th term.
We joined them after their lesson, and we've been paying attention to the details that Ms. Yoshiko pointed out.
We joined them after their pre-lesson, and we could feel that they were paying attention to the details that Ms. Yoshiko pointed out to us during the dance lesson.
Haruka Inoue and Ako Yumiyata have very different ways of learning dance, or rather different types of dance.
Haruka Inoue is the type of person who takes what she's told in her head and breaks it down.
I have an image of Ako Yumiyata as a dancer who tries things out physically and understands them.
I think it's interesting to see such opposites and different patterns.
I hope we can continue to work hard together.
Thank you very much.
I was reminded of that once again.
When I see the dance lessons of the new members, I think back to when I first started dancing.
I came here with no dance experience.
And all the members are experienced dancers.
I felt like I had to work really hard to keep up with them.
I was trying my best to keep up with them.
I didn't feel like I had to make comments to Yoshiko and the others
I felt like I had to make comments to Yoshiko and the others.
I didn't have much verbal instruction on how to look up and check the numbers in detail.
I was never taught verbally, so I was always looking at the members.
I was always watching the members and observing how they were doing.
I remember that I was always watching the members and observing how they were doing.
I hope that the two of us will grow and develop.
I'm looking forward to seeing you two grow and become more and more beautiful like Mr. Nonaka and the other senior members.
I hope you will take notes and absorb everything.
I hope you will take notes and absorb everything you can!
That's all for Morning Musume。23すごいフィーバー!
Haruka Inoue and Ako Yume-Shimoda's dance lesson.
Thank you for watching!
I'm sure something good will come out of it.
I'd like to sing Japanese with English-like nuance as much as possible, and make the rhythm more like English.
Let's start with the A melody.
Photographs from last year, laughing at how young we are
We both acted like adults, but it's so sad.
The head, last year's "Four".
I want to start with a little bit of rhythm.
Last year's photograf, we were young, weren't we?
I'll give it a little nuance.
We're laughing about how young we are.
We're dropping it a little bit.
We're both acting so mature, but it's so sad.
That's right.
Last year's photo graph. We laughed about how young we were.
We're both so mature, but it's so sad.
OK, I think it's good.
Okay, let's try the second half of the A melody.
Two adults, but it's sad...
The matching angled pieces, the memories are so bright...
It's a sign that we've come a long way.
Yeah, just like that!
A little more, like a bouncy feeling.
The matching angle piece... The dazzling memories...
It's a sign that we've come a long way
A little more like that, just a little more bouncy
Feel the back of my hand
Yes!
Two grown-up butts. But it's so sad.
The matching angled pieces... The memories are so bright...
That's how far we've come.
OK!
Okay, let's go to B melody!
Yes!
Here's your proof.
Freshly grated energy
Too big for the future
Are you ready?
Before you overthink it
That's not it.
Ready?
Yeah, yeah, like this.
Let's keep the rhythm the same as before.
Let's make it a little tighter!
Too much freshly-loaded energy for the future
Are you ready?
Want to turn it down a little?
I don't know, "Are you lady?" sounds too much like Japanese.
Are you ready?
It's a little more English.
Before you overthink it.
And the way you bounce.
Yes!
If you cut it all off, it won't bounce.
It'll be too sharp.
Before you overthink it
Just a little bit.
Before
And then, make "that ain't it" a little bit like a line
That's it!
Refreshing
That ain't it
Let's change the nuance just a little there.
Before
Not too much, not too much
Too much, too much
Freshly unloaded energy
Too big a future
Are you ready?
Before you overthink it
That ain't it
Travel Lessons
Thinking
Consideration
Yeah.
But it gets a little muddy.
I'll think about it.
I think.
I'm thinking?
I'll think about it.
I think.
Yeah.
Let's try to be a little more conscious about it.
Freshly Grated Energy
The future is too big
Are you ready?
Go!
Before you overthink it
That's not it.
OK!
Let's move on.
Before I overthink it
That's it!
Traveling Lesson
Next week, it doesn't matter what it is
We each have our own love
We're going to make it happen
It's okay. We're not gonna hold back.
Let's do it!
I'll still be here
Someday I'll be waiting
For the lost
Courage
It's my life
I'll be careful how I use the word "still".
It's a bit like an example
Still
Still...
Still... Still...
Yes, I'll be careful there.
And for the sake of...
I'll drop more firmly
for the sake of
First of all, sing it out
to
Yes, that's enough.
For the sake of
Yes, yes, yes
Yes, yes
I'll do it.
yes, yes, yes
This is hard.
I'm not interested.
Let's do it.
I'll still be waiting for you someday.
For the lost
Courage It's my life
That was really good, wasn't it?
That's how I feel
That's all.
Thank you very much.
This song is very youthful.
The music video is all blue, and I think it's a very refreshing song.
The other day, I was able to see it at the Budokan.
I was really excited when I saw it at the Budokan.
Tsubaki Factory's brightness shines brightly in this way.
I think it's a wonderful song with bright and shiny parts.
In my mind, there was also the direction of the B-melody before the chorus.
The rhythm was very pleasant and detailed, and I really liked it.
It was fun to watch!
It was fun to watch your performance.
It's like she's having a lot of fun chopping it up.
Tsubaki Factory has been working recently.
Satoko Yamagishi and Yumino Kishimoto graduated the day before.
Tsubaki Factory is a new organization just like Morning Musume 2000
I hope to do my best for Hello!
Project, I would like to do my best for Hello!
That's all for Tsubaki Factory.
Yuki It's my life, Mao Akiyama's vocal recording.
Wake up call It's time to wake up It's time to enjoy life It's time to let the sun shine It's time to wake up It's time to wake up It's time to wake up
It's been a while. Thanks for watching.
It's time to say goodbye to Fukami, as Miki Nonaka and Honoka Kobayashi bring you this episode.
We've seen a lot of different videos this time.
I, Kobayashi, was impressed by JuiceJuice's 2023JuiceJuice version in the middle of romance.
This project is possible only with an agency that values instrumental recordings and new members.
I think this is a project that can only be done by an office that values instrumental recordings and new members.
I thought it would be fun if Beyoncé had a chance to re-record some of their old songs as they go through the history of Beyoncé.
I thought it would be fun.
I'd like to see a grown-up boy with glasses.
I'd like to see that.
Yes, I'd like that.
Maybe the members would change.
The members may change.
The members might change, and the cast might change.
I have a lot of imagination.
And in my mind
Morning Musume。23's latest single
The 17th term member of Morning Musume's "Super Fever", Haruka Inoue, and Akiko Yumigeta.
Haruka Inoue and Ako-chan Yumigeta
Haruka Inoue and Akko Yumigeta's dance lesson left a strong impression on me.
It was still summer at that time.
But the season changed to winter.
We did one tour together.
I think both of you have grown up a lot.
I hope that you will continue to grow even more in the future.
I hope that Morning Musume。 Morning Musume。
I would like to point out what we can point out to them
I hope we can create a good situation for them.
I really admire your hard work.
You're doing a great job.
At Apkami, we're going to get behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
We're going to take you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
We'll introduce you to the parts you don't normally get to see.
Please subscribe to our channel!
My partner for this episode is
Miki Nonaka of Morning Musume 23 and
and Honoka Kobayashi of Beyonce Seasonings.
Good bye!
Next time on Apkami
The making of Angulum Red Line music video shooting
and
Morning Musume。23 Sukkoku Fever
Dance lesson with all the members will be shown!
Please look forward to it!
I'm sure everyone will be happy!